[
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [12, 11, 14, 11, 11, 15, 11, 13, 11]?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "12",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [14, 16, 15, 16, 12, 13, 16]?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "16",
        "17",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [13, 17, 13, 15, 13, 13, 16, 14]?",
      "correctAnswer": "13",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "13",
        "14",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [14, 15, 17, 18, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16]?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "16",
        "17",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [19, 16, 19, 18, 17, 19, 15]?",
      "correctAnswer": "19",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "19",
        "20",
        "21"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [17, 20, 18, 16, 17, 19, 17, 17]?",
      "correctAnswer": "17",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "17",
        "18",
        "19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [17, 21, 21, 19, 18, 21, 21, 20, 21]?",
      "correctAnswer": "21",
      "options": [
        "20",
        "21",
        "22",
        "23"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [20, 21, 21, 18, 22, 21, 19]?",
      "correctAnswer": "21",
      "options": [
        "20",
        "21",
        "22",
        "23"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [21, 22, 20, 19, 19, 19, 23, 19]?",
      "correctAnswer": "19",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "19",
        "20",
        "21"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [22, 25, 22, 22, 24, 21, 20, 22, 23, 22]?",
      "correctAnswer": "22",
      "options": [
        "21",
        "22",
        "23",
        "24"
      ]
    }
]